Guide to the Robert Osborn Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- February 1996 Acquisition, 29.84; 123 (boxes) + 53 (Broadsides) + 7 (Rolls)
  - "From Adam", 1966 (Box 145 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 2 (Box 146 (Oversize))
  - "Types of drinks and their drinker types", undated (Box 146 (Oversize))
  - "The process of drinking and some exact drinks", undated (Box 146 (Oversize))
  - Clippings and unidentified drawings, undated (Box 146 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 3 (Box 147 (Oversize))
  - Dilbert posters, 1963; 4 (Box 147 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 147 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Fortune, 1978 (Box 148 (Oversize))
  - Clippings and drawings, undated (Box 149 (Oversize))
  - 'The Poor Speller: a book", undated (Box 149 (Oversize))
  - "Health and disease", undated (Box 149 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 149 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 6 (Box 150 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 5 (Box 151 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for I. Miller, CBS Radio, undated (Box 152 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Family Circle Magazine, 1963 (Box 152 (Oversize))
  - "Bank", undated (Box 152 (Oversize))
  - Tax drawings, undated (Box 152 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 152 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, paintings, and clippings, undated; 5 (Box 153 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Harpers Magazine, 1967 (Box 153 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 9 (Box 154 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 5 (Box 155 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, 3 (Box 156 (Oversize))
  - Drawings related to Communism and the Cold War, undated; 4 (Box 157 (Oversize))
  - "Problem Plants", undated; 4 (Box 158 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 3 (Box 159 (Oversize))
  - "The Diplomat's Confer", undated (Box 159 (Oversize))
  - "Discussions Proceed but Prove Fruitless", undated (Box 159 (Oversize))
  - "Matador", 1955 (Box 159 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and clippings, undated; 4 (Box 160 (Oversize))
  - Navy posters, undated (Box 161 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 3 (Box 161 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 3 (Box 162 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and clippings, undated; 2 (Box 163 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Naval Aviation News, 1977-1978; 4 (Box 163 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 5 (Box 164 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 6 (Box 165 (Oversize))
  - Drawings of cars, undated (Box 165 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, paintings, posters, and clippings, undated; 8 (Box 166 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and clippings, undated (Box 167 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and clippings, undated; 7 (Box 168 (Oversize))
  - Drawings related to cars, undated (Box 169 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 4 (Box 169 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Naval Aviation News, 1975-1976; 4 (Box 170 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 4 (Box 171 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, paintings, clippings, and posters, undated; 4 (Box 172 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 4 (Box 173 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 6 (Box 174 (Oversize))
  - "Drawings for the army through the Flight Safety Foundation", 1962 (Box 175 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 3 (Box 175 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 4 (Box 176 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Orvis, 1981; 4 (Box 177 (Oversize))
  - Unidentifed drawings, undated; 2 (Box 178 (Oversize))
  - "Chapter I Why", undated (Box 178 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 2 (Box 178 (Oversize))
  - "A book to be called Fear", undated; 5 (Box 179 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 3 (Box 180 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for "Osborn on Fear", undated; 4 (Box 181 (Oversize))
  - Clippings and ephemera, undated (Box 182 (Oversize))
  - Drawings related to money, undated; 3 (Box 182 (Oversize))
  - 39 of 40 anti-war large format labels, undated (Box 183 (Roll))
  - "Osborn originals", undated; 6 (Box 184 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 5 (Box 185 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Naval Aviation News, undated; 3 (Box 186 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 186 (Oversize))
  - "Gramps", 1978-1979; 2 (Box 187 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Naval Aviation News, undated (Box 187 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Naval Aviation News, 1972-1973; 2 (Box 188 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Naval Aviation News, undated; 2 (Box 188 (Oversize))
  - "Gramps and Dilbert", 1966 August- November (Box 188 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Orvis, 1981 (Box 189 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and clippings, undated; 2 (Box 189 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 3 (Box 190 (Oversize))
  - Dilbert posters, undated (Box 190 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 191 (Oversize))
  - "Smithsonian", 1990 (Box 191 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 3 (Box 191 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and clippings, undated (Box 192 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 5 (Box 192 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 4 (Box 193 (Oversize))
  - Drawings on paper towels, undated (Box 194 (Oversize))
  - "The Moment of Dying", undated (Box 194 (Oversize))
  - Drawings on paper towels, undated; 3 (Box 194 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated; 5 (Box 195 (Oversize))
  - Drawings on paper towels, undated; 3 (Box 196 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Houghton Mifflin Company, undated; 7 (Box 197 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified drawings, undated; 9 (Box 198 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for Meredith Publishing Company, 1957 (Box 199 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for J.B. Lippincott Company, undated; 6 (Box 199 (Oversize))
  - Painting on glass, undated (Box 200 (Oversize))
  - Drawings for J.B. Lippincott Company, undated; 5 (Box 201 (Oversize))
  - "Osborn on Osborn," autobiography, correspondence and drawings, 1981-1982; 3 (Box 202 (Oversize))
  - Dilbert posters, undated (Box 202 (Oversize))
  - Dilbert posters, undated; 8 (Box 203)
  - Packages
    205-217 (broadsides): Restricted fragile material. Unavailable until further processing is completed. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Unidentified drawings, undated; 2 (Box 204 (Oversize))
    - Restricted fragile
      - Horticulture, 1978 (Box 205 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 206 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 207 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 208 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 209 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 210 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 211 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 212 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 213 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 214 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 215 (Broadside))
      - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 216 (Broadside))
      - Protective case for artwork, undated (Box 217 (Oversize))
  - Broadsides
    - Unidentified paintings, drawing, and collage, undated (Box 220 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 221 (Broadside))
    - Drawings for Hartford, undated (Box 222 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 223 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 224 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and posters for "Osborn on Conflict" exhibition at The Wiliam Benton Museum of Art, The University of Connecticut, Storrs, October 9-November 21, 1982, 1982, undated (Box 225 (Broadside))
    - Drawing for Houghton Mifflin Company, undated (Box 225 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings [some likely Death as a Matador], undated (Box 226 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings [some likely Death as a Matador], undated (Box 227 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 228 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings [some likely Death as a Matador], undated (Box 229 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 230 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, paintings, and collage, undated (Box 231 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 232 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 233 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 234 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 235 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 236 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, some of Marcel Marceau, undated (Box 237 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 238 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and poster for Salisbury Film Society, undated (Box 239 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 240 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 241 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 242 (Broadside))
    - Drawings and paintings relating to drinking alcohol, undated (Box 243 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 244 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 245 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 246 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 247 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 248 (Broadside))
    - Charlie Chaplin drawing, undated (Box 249 (Broadside))
    - Painting of matador with wool yarn, undated (Box 250 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 251 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 252 (Broadside))
    - Drawings and paintings of Charlie Chaplin, undated (Box 253 (Broadside))
    - Drawings and paintings of Charlie Chaplin, undated (Box 254 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings, undated (Box 255 (Broadside))
    - Drawings and paintings of Charlie Chaplin, undated (Box 256 (Broadside))
    - Drawings and paintings of Charlie Chaplin, undated (Box 257 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 258 (Broadside))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 259 (Broadside))
  - Rolls
    - Ann Scoville Kennedy costume ball, undated (Box 260 (Roll))
    - Birthday card of Piano keys to Osborn, undated (Box 261 (Roll))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 262 (Roll))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 263 (Roll))
    - Unidentified drawings and paintings, undated (Box 265 (Roll))
    - "Rape", 1987 (Box 266 (Roll))
- 1999 Acquisitions, 0.21; 1 (box)
  - April 1999 Acquisition
    Former call number: Uncat ZA MS 610.
    - Letters from Osborn to Andrew and Jane Richie, 1949-1985, undated; 10 (Box 264)
  - August 1999 Acquisition
    Former call number: Uncat ZA File 715.
    - Five Christmas cards, 1958-1964 (Box 264)
    - Printed material, 0.21; 1 (box) (Box 273)